<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dabra - shine in managing people</title>
    <link>https://dabra.ai/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dabra - shine in managing people</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:36:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dabra.ai/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer, do you have a great manager?</title>
      <link>https://dabra.ai/posts/developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 16:36:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabra.ai/posts/developer/</guid>
      <description>We help you, developer, to personalize your manager attitude towards yourself. Dabra helps you to have meaningful and impactful 1x1 meetings with your manager. Why is this important? 1x1 meeting with your manager is the main channel where you can convey how valuable you are to the team, what are your personal preferences and what you&amp;rsquo;d like to achieve. Your manager understanding of your strengthes, personal preferences and your contribution is the mast important step towards your feeling of satisfaction at work, higher performance evaluation and sucessful career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development manager, shine in managing people!</title>
      <link>https://dabra.ai/posts/manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 11:06:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dabra.ai/posts/manager/</guid>
      <description>Are your 1x1 meetings meaningful… or a waste of time no one is willing to admit? We make your 1x1 time make a real difference! 1x1 meetings are the main tool managers use to connect to their people, engage and motivate them. 1x1 meetings are where managers spend, and should spend - a lot of time. But is this time with your developers really impactful? Meet Dot! She&amp;rsquo;s here to make a huge difference in 1x1 meetings in your group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>